PERSONAL

- Name
 Sagi Nachum
- ★ Address Nesher 21721 Karmiel
- **Phone number** 0509514805
- ✓ Email
 sagagaga4@gmail.com

INTERESTS

- Music Producer: "Recording, Mixing and Mastering"
- Guitar, Bass, Piano, Singing, Drums
- Drawing, Sketching, Designing album covers

LANGUAGES

English Hebrew



SAGINACHUM

I am a hardworking ,dedicated self taught software developer with over 2 years of programing experience based on autodidactic studying.

Innovative and very initiative, excellent social interaction, tasks and achievements oriented, passionate and willing to learn and develop new programing languages and skills.

"simple & bright" solutions driven person. effective team member that will do what it takes to address company needs.

Programming Languages: React.js, Python, JSX, ES6, JavaScript, Html, CSS, C.

Software: Office365, Visual Studio Code, PyCharm, SolidEdge, SolidWorks, Photoshop, Ableton.



WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2021

Projects Engineer/ Vehicle Accessories Designer

Israel Defence Forces

Redesign of supporting structures for electronic and control devices and reducing their manufacturing costs by 80% <u>together with maintaining their original performances.</u>

Redesign of cameras and sensors holders in autonomous cars. Achieving significant reduction of manufacturing costs and weight.

2018 - Present

Coding Projects

GitHub Link - "https://github.com/sagagaga4"

- "Netflix-Clone" (Firebase axios, TMDB) &"Spotify-Clone" (Spotify API)
 Using React.js taught me the importance of consistent organized
 constructions of code in React, how much you can do with Css flexbox
 and the efficiency of "react hooks" while maintaining fetching data
 functions.
- "Instagram-Like-Bot" using Python (selenium,random,time, self, sys, chrome webdriver, bs4, requests) - amazed me to see how much time I saved by manipulating the code to get systematic daily assignments done for me.
- "Real-Time-Price-Scraping" using Python (bs4,requests) introduced me to an endless number of possibilities where I can use web scraping for.

Sep 2020 - Jul 2020



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Mechatronics Practical Engineer
Ort Braude, Israel

Become a Software Developer
Microsoft

React - The Complete Guide
Academind

Matriculation Degree
Ort Psagot